aa mou uzatte endatte genjou ni zetsubou
Oh man, I'm so damn done with the staus quo
tamekonda itami kokoro de zekkyou
The pain held in, screamed out internally
dare mo shiranai dobunezumi no uta
This is the song of an unknown sewer rat
sawaide kikasemashou
Let me unveil it with a bang
Okay now, Listen up, it’s time for something new
It’s gon get crazy wild, so hold on to this tune
ii deshou ka? koyoi wa boku no Showtime
Are you ready? Tonight is my time, it's showtime
douchouatsuryoku ni kusshita minasan eyo
Listen up, all of you falling in line, eyo
They want a revolution?
Ha! We’ll give it to ‘em!
Take a stand now
My wish is your command!
You want a party?
Follow behind me
kaosu e to goshoutai
You've been invited to pure chaos
kyuuso wa neko kamu ki o tsuke na
But a cornered rat is dangerous, watch out
Rogue Rat RunAway
Gotta get out of this place sewashinai ya
Gotta get out of this place, on the double
Rogue Rat RunAway
chuuyagyakuten hanten sekai (Ratatata)
Day and night flipped around, the world turned upside down (Ratatata)
Rogue Rat Run away
I won’t stay in my own lane tsumaranai ya
I won't stay in my own lane, that's so boring
Rogue Rat Run away
honrou shichau oitsuite
I'll take you on a ride, so try and keep up
kaze no you ni kasumu you ni
Like the wind, like the mist
We'll vanish into the night
dare mo michai nai (no)
Nobody's watching (no)
ima ni mitenasai (yo)
But just wait and see (yo)
boku wa seken no yatsu no "hanatsumami mono"
I'm an outcast in this society
Squeak! Squeak! They run away
Squeak! Squeak! So far away
chuu chuu chuu chuu chuu chuu chuu
Squeak! Squeak! Squeak!
abaremakure
Go buck wild
They say I’m scum, a loser
Too bad, I’ve heard it all before
My music’s all I need
Tell my truth through melodies
Wordplay that makes your heart BOOM!
Start up the party
We gonna get rowdy
noizu ga jama o shite mo
Through the static and the noise
suki wa miseru na kuwarechau zo
Don't show any weakness or you'll be devoured
Rogue Rat Run away
I will keep you on your feet yudan shinai de
I will keep you on your feet, stay on your toes
Rogue Rat Run away
Always keep you guessing madowasete
Always keep you guessing, I'll bamboozle and lead you astray
shirazu shirazu chitsujo midasu
Causing disorder as easily as I breathe
We’ll vanish into the night
Hey ladies & gentlemen yayayaya
Let’s turn these streets into a rave
jiyuu wa doko nano boku ni kachi wa aru no
Where can I find freedom? Is there any value in my being?
genjitsu o kowaseba soko wa shangurira
Let's destroy reality and reach Shangri-La!
Rogue Rat Run away
Gotta get out of this place sewashinai ya
Gotta get out of this place, on the double
Rogue Rat Run away
chuuyagyakuten hanten sekai (Ratatata)
Day and night flipped around, the world turned upside down (Ratatata)
Rogue Rat Run away
I won’t stay in my own lane tsumaranai ya
I won't stay in my own lane. that's so boring
Rogue Rat Run away
honrou shichau oitsuite
I'll take you on a ride, so try and keep up
kaze no you ni kasumu you ni
Like the wind, like the mist
We'll vanish into the night